ATHM Textile Industry Cloth Labels 6524/003 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: Arranged Alphabetically
  - C, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Item 23: Carlisle twills, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Yds. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and royal crest against dark red background; "Dieu et Mon Droit" [God and my Right] written at bottom of crest. Identical to Item 24, in this folder, except for background color. 7 x 11 cm.
    - Item 24: Carlisle twills, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Yds. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and royal crest against dark blue background; "Dieu et Mon Droit" [God and my Right] written at bottom of crest. Identical to Item 23, in this folder, except for background color. 7.5 x 11 cm.
    - Item 25: Carlisle T Twills, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Yds. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against a deep blue, almost purple, background. Crest with two lions in the center with the phrase: "Dieu et Mon Droit" [God and my Right]. 7.25 x 11 cm.
    - Item 26: Ask for Carpenter & Cross new alpaca., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Providence, R.I.: Carpenter & Cross, ca. 1870s. Carpenter & Cross operated under the name Valley Worsted Mills, organized 1872; Carpenter and Cross no longer affiliated with the firm by 1888. Blue lettering on cream background. 2.5 x 2.5 cm.
    - Item 27: Carrollton Mills a standard household fabric woven and finished for the southern trade., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      New York: Cannon Mills, ca. 1900s. Black lettering against a cream background within a dark gold frame. 16 x 10.5 cm.
    - Item 28: Casco Extra Sleeve Linings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed, red lettering within a gold frame, surrounded by a lavender border. 9 x 13 cm.
    - Item 29: Casco Fine Cottons, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      W.H. Forbes & Co., Boston [lith?]. Boston?, n.d. Gold lettering against cream background, surrounded by a gold frame. 14 x 9 cm.
    - Item 30: Untitled label, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Cardboard tag with sailing ship engraved on top. Case____, Style ______, No. ______, ______Yds. N.p., n.d. 7 x 10 cm.
    - Item 31: Cashmere Merino, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed, gold lettering within an oval frame of leaves. 24 x 9.5 cm.
    - Item 32: 1776-1876, Centennial Dwight Company, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Trade mark Registered 1876. Chicopee, Mass.? Dwight Manufacturing Company?. Lithograph? American Bank Note Co., New York. Images of U.S. Presidents with George Washington in the center, surrounded by a frame containing state seals. 24.5 x 21.5 cm.
    - Item 33: Challenge Sleeve Lining, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      No._____ _______Yds. Reen & Trump, Lith., Philadelphia. N.p., n.d. Picture of deer (buck) in center of label. 7.5 x 11 cm.
    - Item 34: Challenge Sleeve Lining, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      No._____ _______Yds. Reen & Trump, Lith., Philadelphia. N.p., n.d. Picture of deer (buck) in center of label. 7.5 x 11 cm. Copy 2.
    - Item 35: Challi 1859 D'Ecosse, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      No.____________ Yds. N.p. Embossed silhouette profile of a man with a short beard in center against gold, oval background. Gold and black lettering. 11 x 14 cm.
    - Item 36: Challi D'Ecosse, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      No.______ ______ Yds. N.p., ca. 1800s. Gold lettering and lithograph (?) of an unknown mill complex within a oval, gold and lavender border. 11 x 14 cm.
    - Item 37: Challi de Laine, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Des. ______ _____ Yds. N.p., n.d. Depicts image of a young woman from the waist up, wearing flowers in her hair and in her right hand, with a necklace of flowers around her neck. 10 x 17 cm.
    - Item 38: Challi de la Princesse, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      No. ______ _______ Yds. N.p., n.d. Engraving of woman elaborately dressed in mid-19th-century fashion, with a crown at the top of the card. 9 x 12.5 cm. (folded).
    - Item 39: Channing Extra Fine Jeans, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Yds. N.p., n.d. Purple lettering within a purple border. 18 x 14 cm.
    - Item 40: Chapman Cotton Mills, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Image of female charioteer driving chariot with four horses, in black oval against green background. 19.5 x 24.5 cm.
    - Item 41: Charles River Cambrics, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      _____ Yds. N.p., n.d. Engraving (?) of two boats racing on [presumably] the Charles River in Boston, with other boats observing the race. Shore in background with a few buildings on the shoreline. 15.5 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 42: Charles River Cambrics, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      _____ Yds. N.p., n.d. Image of sailing ships on body of water; gold lettering, all within gold frame. 17 x 14.5 cm.
    - Item 43: Charter Oak Super Fabric, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Oak tree in ceter surrounded by elaborate frame in gold and green. 15 x 20 cm.
    - Item 44: Chaumont Mills, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering surrounded by an elaborate gold frame that includes children, birds, and insects within the frame. 15.5 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 45: Check Coatings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      No. _____ Yds._____. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering. 14 x 12 cm.
    - Item 46: Cheshire Fancy Linings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., ca. 1870-1872. Lithograph; Ch. H. Crosby, Lith., 46 Water St., Boston. Image in red at center of label is probably St. George Slaying the Dragon. 8.5 x 11 cm.
    - Item 47: Chester Steam Mills, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Chester, Vt.?, ca. 1800s. Black lettering on cream background. 14 x 10 cm.
    - Item 48: Cheviots, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Boston: American Woolen Co., n.d. Gold and red background. 15 x 9 cm.
    - Item 49: Choctaw, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Yds. C.C.P. Moody, Printer, Boston. No later than 1869. Red printing against cream background. 20 x 16 cm.
    - Item 50: City Mills, Read, Gardner & Co. Agents, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Madder Colors. Yds. N.p., ca. 1800s. Image depicts soldier on horseback engaged with man on foot. 11 x 15.5 cm.
    - Item 51: Claremont Extra Heavy Satteens, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed, red lettering surrounded by gold frame. 8.5 x 13 cm.
    - Item 52: Claremont Sleeve Linings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      First Quality. No. Yds. N.p., n.d. Embossed, blue lettering, surrounded by gold frame with white doves set against deep lavender circles. 9.25 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 53: Clarendon A Paddings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against a deep purple background. 11.5 x 15 cm.
    - Item 54: Clarendon AA Paddings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against a gray background. 12.5 x 15.5 cm.
    - Item 55: Clarendon AAA Paddings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against a tan background. 12 x 15 cm.
    - Item 56: Clarendon AAA Paddings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Item 57: Clarendon Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Yds. Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works,, Somerville, Mass. N.p., n.d. Lavender printing on cream background. 16 x 21 cm.
    - Item 58: Clarendon Vest Padding, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against cream background. Royal crest in center with "Dieu et Mon Droit" [God and My Right] written at bottom of crest. 12.5 x 14.5 cm.
    - Item 59: Clarendon Vest Paddings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against cream background. Royal crest in center with "Dieu et Mon Droit" [God and My Right] written at bottom of crest. 12 x 15 cm.
    - Item 60: Climax Blanket, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      10/4 in circle in center. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against tan background. ["Moss Rose" pasted on reverse.] 11.5 x 15 cm.
    - Item 61: Clothiers' Linings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering in elaborate frame against cream background. 16.5 x 14 cm.
    - Item 62: Rich Mohair Corden Mills, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      No. _____ ______ Yds. Sabden, Lancashire, England: Cobden Mills, ca. 1800s. Oval shaped with engraving of mill in center with identical image of a gentleman on either side, probably Richard Cobden, British manufacturer and politician. 24 x 12 cm.
    - Item 63: Cocheco 50 inch sacking, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Style______ Case ______ Yds______. Forbes Co., Boston [Lith.] Dover, N.H.: Cocheco Manufacturing Co., ca. 1868-1875. From Farr Alpaca Company. Black lettering against cream background. 6.5 x 8.5 cm.
    - Item 64: Cocheco fine cambric kid glove finish, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      No. ____ _____ Yds. Dover, N.H.: Cocheco Manufacturing Co., ca. 1857-1862. Chs. H. Crosby, Lith, 3 Water St., Boston. Black lettering against cream background. 13.5 x 10.25 cm.
    - Item 65: Cocheco extra batting 36 inches wide, 9 feet long. One pound roll., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Dover, N.H.: Cocheco Manufacturing Co., n.d. Red lettering against cream background. 11.5 x 8 cm.
    - Item 66: Cocheco Lawrence & Co. Boston No. _____ Yds., 1866; Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Dover, N.H.: Cocheco Manufacturing Co Two women in classical dress, one standing, holding bolt of printed cloth and the other seated, holding pen and tablet; industrial city in background. 13.5 x 18 cm.
    - Item 67: Cocheco prints: fast colors; 35., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Dover, N.H.: Cocheco Manufacturing Co., n.d. Engraving. Yellow background. Shows oval view of mill across pond with boats; three men talking in foreground; floral border. 16.5 x 13 cm.
    - Item 68: Cochineal Dye, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      _____Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against tan background. 3.75 x 5.5 cm.
    - Item 69: Cochineal Dye, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      _____Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against tan background. 3.75 x 5.5 cm. Copy 2.
    - Item 70: Cocheco, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Lawrence & Co. Boston. [Dover, N.H.: Cocheco Manufacturing Co., ca.1866.] Engraving. Two women in classical dress, one standing, holding bolt of printed cloth and the other seated, holding pen and tablet; industrial city in background. Copy 2. 13.5 x
    - Item 71: Extra Colebrook Sheetings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      ______ Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against cream background. Image of Greek goddess (?) in center; railroad in center left, and sailing ships in center right. 16.5 x 10.5 cm.
    - Item 72: Columbia Long Cloth, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering withina royal blue and gold frame. 12.5 x 10 cm.
    - Item 73: Columbian Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Farmhouse surrounded by trees in center; red lettering and red frame. 15 x 19 cm.
    - Item 74: Concord Mills A A A Cambrics., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed, red lettering within gold frame. 9 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 75: Concord Mills A A A Cambrics., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed, red lettering within gold frame. Copy 2. 9 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 76: Concord Mills Superior Linings Silk Finish, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed, red lettering within gold frame. 9.5 x 13.5 cm.
    - Item 77: Connecticut River A A Sheeting, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering within a gold frame. 16.5 x 11.5 cm.
    - Item 78: Connecticut Valley B Jeans, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Yds. N.p., n.d. Green lettering within a green frame against a cream background. 20.5 x 17 cm.
    - Item 79: Continental cambrics., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Lewiston, Me.: Continental Mills, ca. 1868-1875. Image of Washington Monument in center. 11 x 15 cm.
    - Item 80: Continental extra fine corset jeans., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Lewiston, Me.: Continental Mills, n.d. Patriotic images in center and bottom of label, including eagle, drum, American flag, sword and letter of George Washington. Name or graphic has been cut out of label. 20.5 x 24.5 cm.
    - Item 81: Continental Sleeve Lining, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Lewiston, Me.? Continental Mills?, n.d. Black lettering against gold and red background. 8 x 10.5 cm.
    - Item 82: Continental Warranted Madder Prints, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Lewiston, Me.: Continental Mills, n.d. Black lettering against cream background; patriotic images include eagle, drum, American flag at bottom; sword and letter of George Washington in center. 11.5 x 17 cm.
    - Item 83: Conway fine cottons, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Manufactured by Great Falls Manufacturing Co., Somersworth, N.H., n.d. Gold and red lettering within green and gold border. 21.5 x 15 cm.
    - Item 84: Conway superior finish., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Somersworth, N.H.: Great Falls Manufacturing Co., ca. 1848-1869. Bufford, Boston [lithographer]. Black and gold lettering against cream background in black and gold frame. 11 x 14 cm.
    - Item 85: Cordis Mills Cambrics, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      ____ Yds. Millbury, Mass.: Cordis Mills, ca. 1870-1872. Lithograph; Ch. H. Crosby, Lith., 46 Water St., Boston. Image of young woman holding sheaf of flax (?), with mikll buildings in background. 9 x 13 cm.
    - Item 86: Cordis Mills, Millbury, Mass. BB tickings., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.d. Embossed; gold, black and red letterings enclosed within red and gold frame. 15.5 x 20 cm.
    - Item 87: Covington Feather Proof Ticking, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against a red and gold background. 21 x 16 cm.
    - Item 88: Creole Fine Shirtings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      New York: Everdell's Sons, [printer], ca. 1800s. Gold lettering against blue background. 16.5 x 12 cm.
    - Item 89: Crescent Extra Heavy Wigans, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and crescent moon against deep purple background. 12 x 15 cm.
    - Item 90: Crown Extra Fine Wigans, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against a deep purple background. Image of gold crown in center. 15 x 19 cm.
    - Item 91: Crown Glove Finish, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      N.p., n.d. Gold crown and lettering in elaborate gold frame against cream background. 12.5 x 15 cm.
    - Item 92: Cumberland Extra Fine Cambrics, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Yards. N.p., n.d. Black and gold lettering with engraving (?) of mill in center. 12 x 16.5 cm.
    - Item 93: Cumberland Fine Silesias, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Forbes & Co., Boston (printer?). N.p., n.d. Black and brown lettering against tan background. 8.25 x 12 cm.
    - Item 94: Cumberland Fine Silesias, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      _____Yds. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against cream background. 9 x 10.25 cm.
    - Item 95: Cumberland Superfine Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      __Yds. Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works,, Somerville, Mass. N.p., n.d. Black lettering in elaborate frame against gold background. 21.5 x 17 cm.
    - Item 96: Curley's LaFavorita., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Westport, Conn.: Lees Mfg. Co., ca. 1900s. Cream lace netting design against blue background. 20 x 11.5 cm.
  - D, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Dale Steam Mills Family Sheeting, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      N.p., n.d. Gold and red lettering within elaborate frame against cream background. 19 x 14 cm.
    - Item 2: Dartmouth Blue Drillings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Warranted Indigo Blue. Lawrence & Co., Boston. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against orange background. 25.5 x 20.5 cm.
    - Item 3: Dartmouth Colored Flannels, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Extra Heavy. Middlesex Bleachry and Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. Yds. N.p., n.d. Red lettering against yellow background. 25 x 20 cm.
    - Item 4: Dauntless, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      N.p., n.d. Image depicts a man in Tyrolean costume, holding a very large staff, standing on a cliff over water. He is dressed in a green hat, brown jacket, blue shorts, and red socks, and has a luxuriant mustache. 21.5 x 26 cm.
    - Item 5: De Laine, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      No. ____ ____ Yds. N.p., n.d. Embossed; gold/white; dog (greyhound or whippet) in woods. 11 x 14 cm.
    - Item 6: Dennison, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      N.p., n.d. From Farr Alpaca Company. 7 x 9 cm.
    - Item 7: De Witt Mills, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      N.p., n.d. Red and gold lettering within gold frame against cream background. Female figure in classical dress within the letter D. 12.5 x 8.5 cm.
    - Item 8: De Witt, Steam Mills, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Lithograph. C.H. Crosby, Lith., 46 Water St., Boston. ca. 1870-1872. Black lettering against green background. 18.5 x 14.5 cm.
    - Item 9: Dexter Family Cottons, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Lithograph. Ch. H. Crosby, Lithy, 46 Water St., Boston. ca. 1870-1872. Image of trotting horse in center. Black lettering against cream background. 19.5 x 13.5 cm.
    - Item 10: Diagonal Italians, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against an orange banner, surrounded by an orange and black frame. 22 x 10 cm.
    - Item 11: Dodge-Davis Co., Inc., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Style _______ Piece ________ Case _______ Yards ______. Enfield, N.H.: Dodge- Davis Co., Inc., ca. 1900s. The initials DD with an arrow through them in a circle; figure of baseball player in lower right-hand corner. 6.5 x 11.5 cm.
    - Item 12: Domestic, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      N.p., n.d. Image of child wearing hat with feather and handkerchief around neck in circle in center. 18 x 23.5 cm.
    - Item 13: Domestic Shirtings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      The Forbes Lith. M'F'G. Co. Boston [lithographer]. N.p., ca. 1875-18983. Image of woman at spinsning wheel in center in alcove open to outdoors. 20 x 25 cm.
    - Item 14: Dover Steam Mills, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      No. Yds. N.p., n.d. Red, blue and gold with crest; boat in center. 6 x 9.5 cm.
    - Item 15: Dover Extra File Jeans, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      ____Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against green background. 14 x 19 cm.
    - Item 16: Dover Ticking, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against yellow background, surrounded by red and brown frame. 23.75 x 18.5 cm.
    - Item 17: Dril Romantico, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      N.p., n.d. Image of young woman with man in boat on lake, full moon in sky. 18.5 x 23 cm.
    - Item 18: Fancy Drills, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against white background; image of woman warrior (? shield at her side) sitting in center. 9 x 13.5 cm.
    - Item 19: Fine Fancy Drills, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      No_______ Yds_______. N.p., n.d. Embossed; black lettering within gold frame. 8 x 10.5 cm.
    - Item 20: Duck Co. Extra Heavy Drills Warranted Indigo Blue, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against light gray background. 21.5 x 18 cm.
    - Item 21: Dunnell Manufacturing Co. Full Madder Colors, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Lithograph? Pawtucket, R.I.: Dunnell Manufacturing Co., no later than 1899. Image of mill complex, presumably the company works. 17.5 x 13.25 cm. Very similar to Item 22, in this folder.
    - Item 22: Full madder colors., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Dunnell Manufacturing Co. Lithograph; G. Schlegel, Lith. 53 William St. Pawtucket, R.I.: Dunnell Manufacturing Co., no later than 1899. Image of mill complex, presumably the company works. 15.25 x 11 cm. Very similar to Item 21, in this folder.
    - Item 23: Anchor Brand Dwight Co., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Registered in patent office 1875. Chicopee, Mass.: Dwight Mfg. Co., ca. 1875. Embossed; anchor within silver circle; gold sailing ships in upper corners. 17.5 x 22.5 cm.
    - Item 24: Dwight blue drills warranted indigo blue, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      ___Yds. Chicopee, Mass.: Dwight Manufacturing Company, n.d. Black lettering in frame against orange background. 25 x 20.5 cm.
    - Item 25: Dwight Company Chicopee Extra Heavy, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Chicopee, Mass.: Dwight Manufacturing Company, n.d. Embossed; starburst design in center circle against dark blue background with red and gold accents. 17.5 x 17.5 cm.
    - Item 26: Dwight extra fine long cloth., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      P. Schulze 93 Liberty St. NY [printer?]. Chicopee, Mass.: Dwight Manufacturing Company, n.d. 20.5 x 14 cm.
    - Item 27: Extra Fine Dwight Long Cloth, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 28: Dwight Manufacturing Co., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Chicopee, Mass.: Dwight Manufacturing Company, n.d. Gold lettering against purple background. 19 x 13.5 cm.
    - Item 29: Dwight Manufc. Compy. Chicopee, Mass. extra heavy., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      P. Schulze 93 Liberty St. N.Y. [printer?]. Chicopee, Mass.: Dwight Manufacturing Company, n.d. Starburst design in center circle. 17 x 17 cm.
    - Item 30: D M Co. Full 33 Inches Wide, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; gold lettering against red and dark blue background. 17.5 x 6 cm.
    - Item 31: D M Co. Full 36 Inches Wide, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      N.p., n.d. Red and gold lettering against cream background within frame. 17 x 5.5 cm.
    - Item 32: D M Co. Middlesex Bleaching, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 4)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; gold lettering against dark blue background; framed within red and gold background. 7 x 5.5 cm.
  - E, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Eastyarn Yarn. Extra Heavy Worsted for Hand Knitting, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      No.___Color. Brooklyn, N.Y.: Eastyarn, Inc., n.d. Image of colonial woman seated at spinning wheel. Black lettering against red background. 25 x 19 cm.
    - Item 2: Dril Extra 200, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Echeverri Hermanos & Cia. Bogota. Trautmann, Bailey & Slampey, N.Y. [lithographer/printer]. Bogota, Columbia: Echeverri Hermanos & Cia, ca. 1900s. Image of soldier (17th century?) in center blowing bugle with flag with royal crest hanging from it. Bla
    - Item 3: Eclipse Cloaking, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Yds. Middlesex Bleachery & Dye Works. N.p., n.d. Red lettering against yellow background. 25 x 10.25 cm.
    - Item 4: Eclipse Sleeve Linings, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; red lettering against white background within elaborate lavender and gold frame. 8 x 11 cm.
    - Item 5: El Paso Cotton Mill, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 6: Eldon Steam Mills, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against blue background; imiage of mill complex in center. 21.5 x 15 cm.
    - Item 7: Ellerton Shirtings, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering within elaborate red and gold frame. Note the backward "N" in Ellerton. 16 x 11.5 cm.
    - Item 8: Ellerton Mills Drilling. Warranted Indigo Blue, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      ____Yds. C.C.P. Moody, Printer, Boston. [Chicopee, Mass.: Chicopee Manufacturing Company, 1864?]. Black lettering against orange background. 25.5 x 20.25 cm.
    - Item 9: Elm Tree Wigans, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Red lettering against white background; elm tree in center. 13 x 16.75 cm.
    - Item 10: Elwell Mills, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)
      ___ Yds. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and image of peacock in gold within elaborate gold frame, against red background. 12 x 14 cm.
    - Item 11: Intachable irretrecissable solide, Emile roussel Marque deposee Roubaix., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 1)